Guide to the Frederic Ewen Audiotape and Videotape Collection OH.052
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Part 2: Duplicates and Archival Masters. Series II: Reel-to-Reel Tapes. [For Staff Use]
  - Duplicate of OH-52-27 and OH-52-28, Feb 15, 1954, Feb 22, 1954 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-179)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-29 and OH-52-30, Mar 1, 1954 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-180)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-31 and OH-52-32, Mar 8, 1954 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-181)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-33 and OH-52-34, Oct 4, 1954 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-182)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-35 and OH-52-36, Oct 25, 1954, Nov 8, 1954 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-183)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-37, Jan 31, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-184)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-37, Feb 7, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-185)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-38, Jan 31, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-186)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-38, Feb 7, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-187)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-39, Jan 31, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-188)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-39, Feb 14, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-189)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-40, Feb 7, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-190)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-40, Feb 21, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-191)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-41, Feb 14, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-192)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-41, Feb 21, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-193)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-41, Feb 21, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-194)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-42, Feb 14, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-195)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-42, undated (Box 9, Folder OH 52-196)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-43, Feb 28, 1955 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-197)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-44, Mar 1, 1958 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-198)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-45 and OH-52-46, Dec 27, 1959 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-199)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-47, Nov 13, 1960 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-200)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-48, Dec 24, 1967 (Box 9, Folder OH 52-201)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-48, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-202)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-49 and OH-52-50, Jan 26, 1968 (Box 10, Folder OH 52-203)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-51 and OH-52-52, Mar 18, 1968 (Box 10, Folder OH 52-204)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-53, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-205)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-54 and OH-52-55, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-206)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-55 and OH-52-42, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-207)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-56, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-208)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-57, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-209)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-58, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-210)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-67, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-211)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-67, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-212)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-67, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-213)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-75, OH-52-76, OH-52-77 and OH-52-78, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-214)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-75, OH-52-76, OH-52-77 and OH-52-78, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-215)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-75, OH-52-76, OH-52-77 and OH-52-78, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-216)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-79, OH-52-80 and OH-52-81, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-217)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-79, OH-52-80 and OH-52-81, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-218)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-112, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-219)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-151, OH-52-153 and OH-52-154, undated (Box 10, Folder OH 52-220)
- Part 2: Duplicates and Archival Masters. Series III: Digital Audiotapes (DAT).
  - Duplicate of OH-52-44 and OH-52-45 (4 copies), Mar 1, 1958, Dec 27, 1959 (Box 11, Folder OH 52-221)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-44 and OH-52-57 (2 copies), Mar 1, 1958 (Box 11, Folder OH 52-222)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-47 and OH-52-53 (4 copies), Nov 13, 1960, undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-223)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-48 (2 copies), Dec 24, 1967 (Box 11, Folder OH 52-224)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-51 and OH-52-52 (2 copies), Mar 18, 1968 (Box 11, Folder OH 52-225)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-54 and OH-52-55 (2 copies), undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-226)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-55, OH-52-42 and OH-52-56 (2 copies), undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-227)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-58 and OH-52-49 (2 copies), undated, Jan 26, 1968 (Box 11, Folder OH 52-228)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-67 - Tape 1 of 3 (2 copies), Apr 1, 1963 (Box 11, Folder OH 52-229)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-67 - Tape 2 of 3 (2 copies), Apr 1, 1963 (Box 11, Folder OH 52-230)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-67 - Tape 3 of 3 (2 copies), Apr 1, 1963 (Box 11, Folder OH 52-231)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-75, OH-52-76, OH-52-77 and OH-52-78 - Tape 1 of 3 (2 copies), undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-232)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-75, OH-52-76, OH-52-77 and OH-52-78 - Tape 2 of 3 (2 copies), undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-233)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-75, OH-52-76, OH-52-77 and OH-52-78 - Tape 3 of 3 (2 copies), undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-234)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-79, OH-52-80 and OH-52-81 - Tape 1 of 3 (2 copies), undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-235)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-79, OH-52-80 and OH-52-81 - Tape 2 of 3 (2 copies), undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-236)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-79, OH-52-80 and OH-52-81 - Tape 3 of 3 (2 copies), undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-237)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-152 and OH-52-153 - Tape 1 of 2 (2 copies), undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-238)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-152 and OH-52-153 - Tape 2 of 2 (2 copie), undated (Box 11, Folder OH 52-239)
- Part 2: Duplicates and Archival Masters. Series IV: Archival Masters (1/4 inch Reel-to-Reel Tapes).
  - Duplicate of OH-52-27 and OH-52-28 - Tape 1 of 4, Feb 15, 1954, Feb 22, 1954 (Box 12, Folder OH 52-240)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-27 and OH-52-28 - Tape 2 of 4, Feb 15, 1954, Feb 22, 1954 (Box 12, Folder OH 52-241)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-27 and OH-52-28 - Tape 3 of 4, Feb 15, 1954, Feb 22, 1954 (Box 12, Folder OH 52-242)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-27 and OH-52-28 - Tape 4 of 4, Feb 15, 1954, Feb 22, 1954 (Box 12, Folder OH 52-243)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-29 and OH-52-30 - Tape 1 of 3, Mar 1, 1954 (Box 12, Folder OH 52-244)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-29 and OH-52-30 - Tape 2 of 3, Mar 1, 1954 (Box 12, Folder OH 52-245)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-29 and OH-52-30 - Tape 3 of 3, Mar 1, 1954 (Box 12, Folder OH 52-246)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-31 and OH-52-32 - Tape 1 of 3, Mar 8, 1954 (Box 12, Folder OH 52-247)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-31 and OH-52-32 - Tape 2 of 3, Mar 8, 1954 (Box 12, Folder OH 52-248)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-31 and OH-52-32 - Tape 3 of 3, Mar 8, 1954 (Box 12, Folder OH 52-249)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-33 and OH-52-34 - Tape 1 of 4, Oct 4, 1954 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-250)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-33 and OH-52-34 - Tape 2 of 4, Oct 4, 1954 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-251)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-33 and OH-52-34 - Tape 3 of 4, Oct 4, 1954 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-252)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-33 and OH-52-34 - Tape 4 of 4, Oct 4, 1954 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-253)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-35 and OH-52-36 - Tape 1 of 4, Oct 25, 1954, Nov 8, 1954 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-254)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-35 and OH-52-36 - Tape 2 of 4, Oct 25, 1954, Nov 8, 1954 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-255)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-35 and OH-52-36 - Tape 3 of 4, Oct 25, 1954, Nov 8, 1954 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-256)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-35 and OH-52-36 - Tape 4 of 4, Oct 25, 1954, Nov 8, 1954 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-257)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-37, Jan 31, 1955 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-258)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-37, Feb 7, 1955 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-259)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-38, Jan 31, 1955 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-260)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-38, Feb 7, 1955 (Box 13, Folder OH 52-261)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-39, Jan 31, 1955 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-262)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-39, Feb 14, 1955 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-263)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-40, Feb 7, 1955 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-264)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-40, Feb 21, 1955 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-265)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-41, Feb 14, 1955 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-266)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-41, Feb 21, 1955 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-267)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-42, Feb 14, 1955 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-268)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-42, undated (Box 14, Folder OH 52-269)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-43, Feb 21, 1955 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-270)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-43, Feb 28, 1955 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-271)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-44 - Tape 1 of 3, Mar 1, 1958 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-272)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-44 - Tape 2 of 3, Mar 1, 1958 (Box 14, Folder OH 52-273)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-44 - Tape 3 of 3, Mar 1, 1958 (Box 15, Folder OH 52-274)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-47 - Tape 1 of 3, Nov 13, 1960 (Box 15, Folder OH 52-275)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-47 - Tape 2 of 3, Nov 13, 1960 (Box 15, Folder OH 52-276)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-47 - Tape 3 of 3, Nov 13, 1960 (Box 15, Folder OH 52-277)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-51 and OH-52-52 - Tape 1 of 3, Mar 18, 1968 (Box 15, Folder OH 52-278)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-51 and OH-52-52 - Tape 2 of 3, Mar 18, 1968 (Box 15, Folder OH 52-279)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-51 and OH-52-52 - Tape 3 of 3, Mar 18, 1968 (Box 15, Folder OH 52-280)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-54 and OH-52-55 - Tape 1 of 4, undated (Box 15, Folder OH 52-281)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-54 and OH-52-55 - Tape 2 of 4, undated (Box 15, Folder OH 52-282)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-54 and OH-52-55 - Tape 3 of 4, undated (Box 15, Folder OH 52-283)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-54 and OH-52-55 - Tape 4 of 4, undated (Box 15, Folder OH 52-284)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-56, undated (Box 15, Folder OH 52-285)
  - Duplicate of OH-52-112, undated (Box 15, Folder OH 52-286)